Pluto
<Shouldn't we report this to Commander Goer, on planet Balan?>
<We lost a carrier.>
<And what do you think will happen if that opportunist reports this to headquarters?>
<We'll deal with it ourselves.>
<We'll destroy it from long range. Ready the planet bombs.>
<Yes, sir!>
<We cannot fail.>
Bombing at Zone 7 Management Center Building
Activate
Episode 2
Toward a Sea of Stars
Believe
A star will shine today
Above your head
Even far away
It pours down onto us
The same brilliance
Surely it is the way to return
A small hope to light it up
To the sky you gaze upon
If I pray to eternity for a connection
Even in days of sorrow
Can we meet once again?
The heart knows it is all right
Will it be a mutual promise?